Welcome dear rockets, how are you all, today we are
going to see the dark planet.
At the beginning of the movie, a rating voice tells us
that this is the time 2157 where humans have
completely taken over the earth, all the
fighting is over, aisi aisi daaba  It has been developed by
which one pill can eliminate every disease of the world
and now that humans have
taken control of the Earth, they
thought of taking a step forward so that they
can find another planet like the Earth and where
extra terrestrial life is present.
Now we see a boy named  To
save his life, he has to land on the nearest planet.
Now after reaching that planet,
as Max comes out of his spaceship, the
spaceship gets
destroyed due to the explosion, due to which Max's
contact with the Earth is completely lost.  Neither can
he go to Earth from here nor can he
contact and call for help. The
poor guy gets worried thinking what should
I do? This is a completely new place,
but after controlling himself for a while,
he decides.  He thinks that he should explore this planet
so that he can get some kind of
communication system
through which he will be able to call for help from the Earth.
Also, one good thing about this planet is that
it is exactly like the Earth's atmosphere so
that  Max does
not have any problem in breathing. Now as soon as Max
moves forward, there comes a soldier named Jeff
who lives on this planet.
Max does not understand his language,
so he uses the translating device
in his work.  Jeff puts it on so that he can
understand his language and talk to him, after which
Jeff hands Max over to the people of authority
so that he can handle it himself, then they
put some kind of helmet on Max's head and see all his memories on the screen.
Now all the
soldiers take Max to the city's capital,
where while passing through the way,
Max also sees the common people living on this planet
who are looking for food.  They are
fighting with each other for the things to drink.
Seeing the whole environment around, it seems
that the people here are fighting for freedom,
then while moving ahead, Max's eyes
fall on a tower. The people here are fighting for this tower.  They
believe that it
protects them from the enemies, but then suddenly the
tower explodes, the debris of which falls
on Max and all the people present along with him, many
people are killed in this, but the tank in which
Max was present in it, a soldier named James
also joins him, so Max
somehow gets out of the tank and comes away,
which saves both their lives. Then
James tells Max that if our
enemies have any business, they are always in this.  They
wanted to destroy the tower, in which today they have succeeded,
now they don't know what will be their next step,
now Max is also surprised to hear
that here also the fight does not end anywhere,
meaning on the other hand, the head of the Special Research
Department, whose  His name is Nomad. He
tells one of his friends, Frank, that
wherever Max is, find him immediately and bring him to me.
I suspect that he might be a spy.
Then Frank agrees and sets out to
find Max.
So we also see a man named David,
he also asks his partner to find out as much
information as possible about Max,
while Frank is
taking Max to Nomad
when he gets a seizure attack.  And because of this,
his car meets with an accident,
then after this incident, a crowd of people
gather there and taking advantage of this opportunity,
Max immediately runs away from there and
starts exploring the entire city
from there.  Max goes to a club
where he meets a girl named Rada,
who is actually James's sister.
They start talking
where Max tells her about himself
but then their argument is interrupted by others sitting there.
The man does
not do anything to Max right now but when Max
comes out of the club with Rada, he comes there with his
goons who
had come there with the intention of killing Max but
Max is very relieved.
Seeing his bravery, Rada brings him to her home
and then James also comes there.
Now I ask them about this planet, on
which both of them tell
that apart from this planet, we have to find other planets too.  It is
not allowed to extract information about any place
and the city where we live is
run by an authority whose leader is a man named Tom. He has
installed towers in the entire city for the protection of all of us, but the authorities of the rest of the city
want that all  The city should
work together but our city does
not want this, so the rest of the city has
become our enemy who
keeps attacking us and
wants to destroy us completely. Max is shocked to know this,
after which James  He
also starts training Max as a soldier
so that he can protect himself from enemies.
Also, Rod and Max
gradually start liking each other.
Now, at the behest of the Captain, Max and James
along with some other soldiers  They go on a mission,
according to that mission, they have to catch some rebels
whom the authorities suspect
that they may have
helped the enemies in exploding the tower. When Max
goes to those rebels, he finds them all
absolutely normal.  They appear to be human beings
who just like to live peacefully with their families,
so how can these people be rebels,
it comes to one's mind,
but still they are caught and
handed over to the authorities, where they are treated in very
bad ways.  After killing him, he is asked
whether he had helped the enemy in blowing up the tower on
which all those people,
despite suffering so much,
refuse to accept that they had
brought down the tower. Now Max tells James.
I don't think the Revels are bad, they
are just ordinary people whom we are forcibly
oppressing, so from now on I
will protect them from the people in authority.
Whatever happens, James forbids him to do so
but Max agrees with him.  One does not listen
and when Captain orders Max that
you have to kill all the rebels, then on the
orders of the Captain, he brings them to the place
where they were to be killed, but
after coming there, he secretly kills all those rebels in the
forest.  He also drives him away and
when the captain comes to know about this, he gets
furious and then Max
tells him that these are not all ruffians but
innocent people who are being tortured,
so I don't kill them.  And
then on hearing this, the Captain shoots Max,
seeing which James also gets scared
and tries to help him
but the Captain forcefully takes him away from there.
Now after some time, Max's
eyes start falling from the Rubbles' base.  But it opens, those people who
saved Max and treated him,
tell Max the truth about the authority, that all the people of the authority have
taken the people of the entire city under their control
and the tower you saw is the same
tower which is in the city.  In
fact, it does not save us from enemies
but releases such radiation
that all the people come under the control of radiation
and once a person comes
under the control of radiation, he will hear,
say and do the same thing.  Whatever the authority asks him to
do, that person becomes a puppet of the authority,
but yes, there are some people
who are not affected by radiation
and whenever the wave of radiation passes through that person,
he only gets seizure attack
and  Due to this attack, the authority comes to
know that Dishon is not having any effect on these people,
hence they label such people as
rebels and give orders to kill them
so that all the rebels do
not come together against the authority and it seems that your  There is the
same special thing inside too, that's why Dashan is
not affecting you. Now Max gets more surprised to hear this
and decides that he will
somehow have to bring the truth about the authority to the people.
Max tells Abhi to listen to
me.  We should blow up all these towers
so that all the authorities
go out of control. They all agree on this,
then Max leads his team and
goes near a tower. After leaving, they
start killing all the soldiers.  Therefore, the
soldiers also attack them
in which many of Max's comrades are killed,
but still Max succeeds in blowing up the tower by planting a bomb,
but many of his comrades have also been killed,
so he is very sad about this.  He also feels sad,
now Max comes to James from there,
seeing him he is both surprised and happy, then
Max tells him the truth about the tower, but
James does not fully believe
that the authority can do this.  It does
not happen that this tower is not protecting them
but is helping them in making them puppets,
that is because James has
spent his entire childhood here, but in the
meantime, soldiers come there and
attack them, who keep them here.  They
had come with the intention of capturing him because the
soldiers had learned that Max had
found out the truth and now his team too,
including James and Rada,
Max and the others now try to fight them
but the number of soldiers is too great.  It
becomes too much, due to which they are caught,
after which they are locked in jail
where Max has other friends.
After leaving, Max meets Jeff,
who is also locked here because of being a rebel.
Max tells them all
that we have to get out of this prison by any means
so that we can destroy all the towers and
save people from the clutches of the authority,
on which they all agree, after this
Noma comes to David and says  I heard
you're looking for someone named Max.
If you have him,
hand him over to me. I
want to tell your boss Tom about him, but David
says he doesn't know Max, and
also David. Cesar.  An attack comes, which
clearly means that he is also one of the rebels
but he has kept his identity hidden from everyone. On the
other hand, Max
secretly comes out of the prison with Jeff and a prisoner
and from there they attack the tower.  They go out to explode
but after coming a short distance they are
attacked by some robots, so they
all quickly start hiding here and there to
escape from all the robots, while
when David comes to know that Max's body is also revealed.  He
is like a person on whom no radiation has any effect,
then he immediately orders one of his companions to
go and find Max from anywhere and
bring him to me, he is also alive but
remember, no one has any clue about this.
It should happen otherwise I will
not leave you alive and on this he agrees to his words.
Here Max tells Jeff and the man
that what if he blows up the center of authority
from where they control all the towers,
meaning from where all the  The
towers get power, this will mean that
all the towers will shut down simultaneously but
Jeff says that this is not possible. The towers have been
designed in a very different way
that no one knows
how and from where they operate.  Now after
hearing this, Max again gets worried as to
what to do if he does. Jeff further tells
that there are many people living in the South who are
not affected by radiation but they have nothing to do with the
people of our city.  They wo
n't even help us. Just
then an automatic tank comes there and
starts attacking everyone, but Max
somehow risks his life and enters the tank
and switches off its automatic control system.
Now Max is alone in the tank.  He
comes near the border of the city with a tank so that he can
go south from there and
convince them to join his team, but
after crossing the border, soldiers stop Max.
Max sees James among them,
so he kills him.  After putting it in his tank, he
breaks all the barricades and comes outside the border,
where on the way he again
tries to convince James that the
authority is really controlling everyone through radiation, only then
James
believes this.  This happens because
after crossing the border the effect of radiation had reduced on him,
due to this he becomes very angry
that till date we have been cheated
and he also decides that now he will
not leave the authority. Max on this  He
tells him about his plan that we are going to the South and will ask for
help from the people there
so that he can destroy all the towers, on this
James also agrees to help him in this thing
and with this scene the
movie ends.  Looks like it ends here, the
story will come in the second part ahead of it,
coming soon friends, see you next
with the best movies. If you liked this video,
then like it and
subscribe the channel, take care of yourself and finally
thanks for
watching
[Music]
B