This story starts with a concert where
many people had come, everyone was having a lot of fun
but it is shown that suddenly some
parasites fall from the sky to the ground, one of these
parasites goes into the ear of a boy who came to the concert.  As soon as it
entered the boy's ears, it
seemed as if the parasite had
taken the boy under its control. Within no time,
the boy's mouth broke into five parts.
He had now become a monster.  He
attacks everyone who came to the concert with a big ton of skull.
He was killing everyone here one by one
and that is why there is
no chaos here. Scene stumbles. We are
shown a girl named Zion in a mall.
She works as a cashier here,
where today when a customer misbehaves with her,
Zion ignores him
because she did not want to create issues for herself,
but the
customer had learned about her ignoring her, she sat outside the mall.  He
was determined to take revenge. As soon as
Zion comes out of the wall, this boy
first hits her bike with his car
and quickly
gets out of his car at Zion's Kirni and attacks her badly with a knife.  She was
badly
injured and the boy threw her there on the roadside. It is
shown that
where Zion was lying injured, there
was a parasite which
went inside Zion's body from the place of his wound. When Zion
regained consciousness,  She finds herself in the hospital,
where her uncle is also present, who is
a police officer. He is worried about Zion.
He asks Zion
what happened to you. Zion tells
that she was attacked by a man with a knife.
In response to which the doctor standing nearby
tells Zion that if you were
attacked then there
were not even any marks on your body and
Zion was also shocked and upset after hearing this
because the way she was attacked.  What happened was that she was
confident that she would be able to survive. Now at the same
time, we are shown a boy named Kang Vo. He is a body hunter and has come to kill a gangster. Along
with the gangster, he also had a lot of security
and  When he could not kill the gangster,
his life was in danger. To
save his life, he ran away from here to his
sister's house, where he noticed
that his sister was behaving very strange.  When he
asks about his younger sister, she says that she has gone out
but the good thing is that her phone and all the
important things were at home. Kang also sees an
invitation from some organization on the same table. He is yet to know
about it.  He does
n't ask his sister anything. The scene stumbles.
We are again shown Zion who is
going back to her job but she
notices that many people are
looking at her strangely on the way and in this situation
she becomes very worried.  They get scared, the scene cuts
and we are shown an unknown girl
who had brought a man to an empty
building. Suddenly
many more people also come inside this building and
it is someone else who has brought the man to this building.
She suddenly broke into five pieces and
turned into a monster. It was
revealed that she was also a parasite who had
brought this man into this building to kill him
and the military people were informed about all these parasites.
Before all the parasites can kill this man together, the
military people
reach here to save him and start attacking all the parasites with their guns.
Almost all the parasites were killed
but some run away from here.  They also
succeed, that man's life is saved and
we come to know that the
name of the military group that attacked here is
D.Gray, whose mission is to eliminate these parasites from the land
and their leader was
Zoe.  Who had a parasite whose
head was closed with a helmet
and through this parasite she was able to
reach the other parasites, where it is shown
that Zion is being chased by some strange people from which
Zion was running away.
And suddenly now a man and a woman come in front of him,
both of them together tell Zion
that you are like us, you are a parasite and that is why
now you should join our gang. The
purpose of this gang
was to eliminate humans from the earth.  These parasites that had
descended from the sky to the earth were actually
aliens who found the earth
a good place to live and that is why they
wanted to kill all the humans and live here. It turns out
that no one was keeping all these things secret.
Kang was listening, he had come here chasing his
sister about whom
he was feeling that she was doing strange activities for a long time.
After these two parasites left from here, she
also came here secretly.  Had started leaving but
Zion comes to know about it and now Zion
takes out a tentacle from her mouth and
catches it and drops it close to her. She holds this man and
says that
you have to do only as much as I say. As soon as she says this
She had become unconscious. When she regained consciousness,
Kaon told her that in unconsciousness he
talked to Kangu a lot. He
told Kangu that there is a parasite inside me which
can control my mind for just 10 minutes in the whole day.  And the
attacks that happened on him that day were actually cured by
Parasite.
After telling all this, Congo leaves and
Zion is upset that even
she did not know these things, so she went to Congo.
She gets worried and sits down with a diary
and writes on it, 'Have I really
become a parasite?' As soon as she writes this,
she falls asleep and when she wakes up, she
sees that there are many more things in her diary.  It was
written that the answers to all the questions asked by him were
now written in his diary. Seeing this, he got
scared. It was written in the diary that yes, there
is a parasite inside you and that day
when you got chapped, that is,
a parasite was running inside your wounds.
I was the one who healed your wounds. If
I had not healed you, I would have
died myself. Now because I have saved your life,
my first priority is to
protect you and only after that I
will do anything else. All the things present there.  The
parasite present inside Zion had written it
and upon realizing this he is very
upset. Here we are shown the leader of Gray Gang,
Xiao, who had called a meeting.
Inside this meeting, we
also see Zion's uncle Xiao here.  She was
telling everyone about parasites. She had
caught a parasite with tentacles and she was
telling her people here how
parasites control the minds of humans. She
also told everyone here some characteristics of those humans who are parasites.
After hearing this, Zion's
uncle comes to Zion because he
suspects that Zion has also become a parasite
because it was not common for his wounds to heal so quickly that day.  They
pluck a hair from his head and see that that hair had
not withered like a human being turned into a parasite. At this time, his uncle gifts him a kitchen and leaves. It is
shown
that at this very moment Kangaroo's sister came to
meet him.  Zion, who had previously met him and
asked him to kill the parasite gang,
tells Stum Sun that our
father wants to meet you because you are a
parasite who is
able to live very well among humans.
Without answering many questions, she goes with him
to a church where she sees that
apart from him, many parasites had also come.
Father was telling all of them that the purpose of our coming to this earth is to
destroy all the humans present here.  Because this
planet is suitable for us to live, we see
that Kang had also come here chasing his sister
and in a room of this church,
he finds his younger sister dead.
He was still in shock that here.
A parasite sees him and
in anger over his sister's death, Kang
attacks the parasite with his axe.
All the parasites come to know about this attack on the parasite
and they all
start chasing Kang Wo.  Hai had
run towards the forest. Zion, who was standing there, was
not able to understand what to
do. In the chaos, the kitchen
which her uncle had given her falls from her hand.
Kang was running here on the other side.
The gangsters whose leader he wanted to kill had come in front of him, the
gangster was in front and the
guard behind was trembling and he would have said that
now his life was in trouble from both the sides and
he felt that now he was going to die.  At
this time, luck favors him.
Parasites find the gangsters trembling,
that is why they
attack the gangsters and as soon as they get the chance,
they run away from there.
Here on the way, they meet Zion who
tells them to  That your life is in danger,
you should run away from here right now. Only these
two run away from here and reach a car
which belonged to Kang Woo's friend. They were
sitting in it and were running away from here when
suddenly a parasite attacks their car.  Seeing
this, the parasite inside Zion
also wakes up, who had
told Zion that it
is his responsibility to protect him. The parasite inside Zion
was now taking it from other parasites.  The
car in which these people were sitting gets
out of balance and they meet with an accident. The
CO had left the car within no time
but now Kang Vo's life was
in danger again because
after this accident,
Here, first Zion
kills the other parasite and then
reaches Kangu to save him.
She saves Kangu's life with the help of her big tentacle and
brings him out.
Joey, the leader of the Gray Team, is shown
learning about the case of Seyon who was attacked by a man
and is shocked to hear that all of his wounds
and scars were healed within minutes.
She becomes convinced
that there must be a parasite inside Zion too,
about which she investigates with
Zion's uncle. Here Cain Book
and Zion together tell Zion's uncle
about the parasites present in the church
and here Zion's  Uncle tells her that
I have to meet you, hearing which she also got nervous.
He tells Kang that I feel
that my uncle has got suspicious about me.
Gangu tells her not to worry, I
will go with you if anything happens.
Here Jio also comes to know
that Zion's uncle is going to meet him,
hence he puts his spies
behind Zion's uncle so that
he can also know the reality of Zion. Zion's
uncle who takes him to a park.  I had come to meet him. He
asks her, "So tell me, what exactly is
going on? Have you become a parasite?
Before Zion knew anything,
Xiao comes from behind with a gun in her hand.
She went to kill Zion but  Kang takes
Zion away from here and now
Gray Teen's people go after them, at
this time Zion tells Kango that you
run away from here, I
will save myself somehow and it is shown that Save  The
parasite inside him wakes up. Kang
manages to escape from here and
while running, he sees that someone has
killed Xiao's husband. We already
know that Xiao's husband was also a
parasite.  On whose face Jio always
kept a helmet tied and because of that
she was able to catch parasites. Here Jio was about to
catch Zion. We see
that suddenly Zion falls unconscious.
Jio was sure that he was a parasite.
But here Zion's uncle tells everyone,
look, there is no hole in his head,
he is a common man, now they were talking only when
someone comes and tells Jio that
someone has killed her husband and now Jio  She
takes off her husband's helmet and
puts it on Zion because with the help of this helmet,
all the parasites could be controlled.
Zion is now brought to the military base.
Here, during the meeting with his senior, Xiao comes to
know that
he has a  And they have caught the parasite. They were
talking about Zion,
but sitting here, Zion's uncle quickly
says, no, he is not a parasite,
he is a normal human being whom these people have
captured with him.  All the tests have also been done
and all the tests are showing
that there is no parasite inside him. The
authorities are shown the tests done on Zion's brain
where no parasite was seen anywhere in his brain.
Zion's uncle authorities.  They tell that
Zion had become unconscious after seeing the military
and now she is in a coma. Her
mental condition was already not good and if she
dies then who will be responsible.
After listening to Zion's uncle, the authorities send Zion to
head.  She gives orders to shift the quarter. The
scene cuts to show us Zion
who is currently in a coma. She
was dreaming in a coma and in her dream she
now sees the same parasite that was
controlling her body.  She
tells Zion that I did not send you into a coma.
If I had not done this to you, you would have been killed.
You would have come under the control of that helmet.
This parasite tells Sun that I am a
little weak, I am like any other parasite, like
any other human being.  I can't change the shape of the body,
that is, I can't change its body, that
's why I have to stay hidden inside you.
When I came inside you,
you were injured. To keep myself alive,
I had to treat you first and
I am yours.  I protect myself so that
I can remain safe.
Here Zion also
tells her story to this parasite, the story of her childhood
where her parents used to beat her a lot
and to save her life, she got her
dad arrested.  Mom,
who had remarried,
never adopted Zion and
in such a difficult situation, Zion's uncle brought him
up and at this time Parasite
explains to him that you have to be strong yourself.
Sean's stumble is shown to us.
Seon's uncle finds out about Jo Kang Woo
because he was last seen with Seon.
This gang is the one who was
trying to escape from the city. Seon's uncle
catches him and asks him
where he is.  Who are you and what were you doing with Zion?
Do you know the truth about Zion?
In response to which the boy says yes,
I know he is not a parasite, there is definitely
a parasite present inside him but
he is completely a human being and  She wants to help us,
here Zion's uncle
tells her that now Zion is being taken to the head quarters
and there experiments will be done on him. The
gang tells him
that why experiment on Zion only
when he is in your own team.  There is a parasite.
I had seen that
a member of your team had
killed the parasite who was Xiao's husband. This was
shocking for Sayo's uncle. Sayo's uncle
shows him the group photo of his team from which
he recognizes Kang.
Now Kang
asks Wo Se's uncle what is the purpose of capturing me,
then here Seon's uncle
tells him that I need your help, as
soon as he goes to the head quarter,
experiments will start on Seon and he
You will die, all you have to do is go to the police station and
steal the remote that controls Parasite's helmet and even if you are caught,
I promise you that I will get you
freed. Campu agrees to this task. On the
other hand, the military man who
became Parasite is  He calls Parasite Father and
tells him that the military has caught a parasite named Zion,
they will
experiment on him, he is being taken to the
military headquarters
and if you save him on the way,
then all of you will be saved.  It is shown
that Kango has also come to the military office to complete his mission. As soon as
he goes inside, he
fights with a soldier, beats him and
wears his clothes before he
steals the remote. Who comes here and takes the remote of the helmet
and  Considering Kanfu to be a military
soldier, she assigns him duty that
he will remain in this systematic vehicle in
which Zion was being taken to the head quarter.
On the way, this truck has to
stop because there was a lot of traffic
jam ahead and this traffic was known.
Actually, these parasites
want to save Zion from here, the gray team
i.e. the military people attack all these parasites
and the parasites also
start fighting with these people with their big tactical weapons. This fight continues for a long time.
And taking advantage of this fight, Gangu
fights with Jeong and takes the remote of Seo's helmet.
He quickly opens Seo's helmet and
saves her and runs away from there. We
see that Jeong had also regained consciousness on the way
and  Here Cain tells her
that your uncle is in the car behind us
and the military man sitting with him is
also a parasite. On
hearing this, Cain gets scared. Now she was
running to save her uncle.  On the other
hand, that military guy had brought Zion's uncle
to the father of Parasites and after
coming here he tells him that I
was tired of doing honest jobs where I did
not get paid at all and that is why
I decided to support Parasites.  While
he was talking about the same thing,
father
without wasting any time kills Seyon uncle with a big tentacle of his mouth
and Seyon reaches here and keeps watching this,
her heart was hurting very much.  She had now become
angry and now
she fights with Father by changing her mouth into a big tentacle
but as we know earlier that
Zion's parasite does not have that much strength,
he is not able to fight Father completely here
and due to this  Before Father can do any harm to him,
Cain takes his car and
Zion leaves with it.
Here it is shown that Father shifts the ship and
transforms himself into Zion's uncle so
that he can stay among the military and on
their side.  The
scene is cut and
shown to us from a past in which
Kang Woo's sister was being killed. When she
came home, she saw that the father was with her sister.
The girl met her sister.  She says
that you are unwell, why have you come to the father,
you should
go to the doctor and after listening to her words, the father
feels that maybe she has
known the reality of her becoming a parasite, that is why they have
decided to kill this girl.  To
save her life, she also sends a message to Congo,
but before she could send this message,
her own sister had
brutally killed her by removing the tentacles from her face. The
scene again takes us to the
meeting of the authorities.  It is shown
where all the authorities are angry at Joey
because of him, Zion got away from him.
Zion here apologizes to them for her mistake
and says that she
will catch him soon. Authority Sun tells Sun that the
coming  There is going to be a big festival in their city in a few days, they ca
n't cancel this festival and
before the festival comes, they have to handle the whole situation
or it is shown that Kang
takes Seon to a friend's house.  Had come
and tells Zion to rest,
we will leave this city as soon as the morning dawns, but
Zion answers him, no, I will
not leave this city. The parasites of this city have
killed my uncle and
I will kill them only after destroying them.  I will stay at night.
Sayo gang takes some money from them and runs away from here. The
first thing they go out of here is
call Joey, the leader of the gray team
who was on the mission to kill the parasites. She
tells him that there are two such people in your office.  There
are officers who are parasites but
you don't know about them. Xiao replies
how can this be possible. We had
scanned everyone. Zion says no.
Here Zion tells her that I saw my
uncle dying in front of my eyes
and  Now a person disguised as him has
come to your office. Zion now
calls Joe to meet him alone. Zion and Geo
talk here. Geo tells him that if
both of them are parasites then why did they tell us
about the parasite's base.
In response, Zion says that
she may also have a trick. Jio says,
okay, let's assume that she has accepted your words,
if she is cheating then you
too can cheat, if you are really a
human being.  Work together with us for us. As
soon as he says this, many
soldiers come behind him who were about to make Zion
wear the helmet, that is, Jio had betrayed Zion
and now Zion jumps from the roof to save her life.
Kang Woo came to help her, he
actually didn't want to leave Seon alone.
Kang Woo and Seon were on the way when
Kang Woo gets a call from his friend,
where Kang Woo's sister was talking on the phone as if in a friendly manner.
About whom we already
know that she has become a parasite
and has also murdered her own sister.
She now tells Gango that I
am with your friend, if you want to save her
then come back home quickly.  If
not take Zion or I will kill him. Cango
tells him that he will come home with Zion
but they should not do anything to his friend.
Zion also wanted to save Cango's friend
but the problem was that the
parasite 3 inside Zion.  She had slept for an hour,
hence Gangu's sister would never listen to him
considering her to be a parasite or Gangu
gives her the idea that you should go there and
act as if you have a
parasite inside you and after listening to Gangu, both of them
go there.  She
starts acting as if she has been controlled by a parasite.
She tells Gang Vo's sister
that you leave this self, I am
ready to go anywhere with you,
but from her words, Kango's
sister here recognizes her.  She realizes that there is no parasite inside her at this
time.
She now calls for an attack on Zion to kill him,
but to save Zion,
Canu now attacks his sister.
In anger, Canu's sister attacks all
three with her tentacles.  Attacks and
here Kang Woo's friend sacrifices his life to save Kang Woo and Seyon's life.
Here he controls Kang Woo's sister and
gives both of them a chance to escape from here. Here Seyon calls Joey again.
She tells him that you should not go to
their base following the words of those parasites
that if you go there to save your life,
we will kill you and your officers there. Jio still did
not believe her, he tells her.  I am also
a human being, they can kill me too,
you keep the phone on, let's see
who will kill whom, it is
shown that all the
military officers will go to that church and
shoot and kill all the parasites.  Not
only this, the parasite present in Zion's uncle's face
also kills one of his comrades to
make Joe believe that he is
a human. Seeing him do this, Joe now
says to Sun, see, everyone was killed and my
team.  There is no parasite in me. Now look,
after all the parasites have been destroyed, now it is
your turn. On hearing this, Sun disconnects the phone. At the end
of the scene, it is shown that the
parasite himself is holding a conference in the face of Zion's uncle.
He
himself tells everyone that all the parasites have been
killed except two parasites,
one of which was Zion and the other was Ngbu
's sister, as soon as they catch and kill them,
their mission will be completed.
Zion and Kongu are also watching this news.  On the other hand,
Kangoo's sister also asks Seon Kongoo, what is
all this happening, why did this parasite
kill its own people, to which
Kang Woo says that this is his big
plan, in the next few days, there will be a massacre in this city.  There is
going to be a festival in which the
mayor will come here and that parasite wants to kill the mayor and
rule over this city by taking the mayor's face.
Now these people were talking
that here Seon gets a call from Kang Woo's sister
who tells him that  It was said that that father
now wants to kill us, which is absolutely
wrong. We parasites did not come to earth so that
we do not rule over humans. We are
parasites. We came here only to eat humans.
Before now, that father wants to kill
us.  Kill me, I have to kill that father and
I need your support in this. Abi father was the
man who had killed Zion's uncle.
She just wanted to take revenge, so she
agrees with Kango's sister.
After Zion's uncle's press conference.  Zoe
also becomes suspicious of them because earlier
Zion's uncle always talked about saving her
and now he was exposing her.
When she asks Zion's uncle about this,
he does not give her any answer. Finally
now the festival.  The day also comes and the mayor
also comes to celebrate the festival.
Here Zion calls Joey and says that the
man working in the military in the form of my uncle is a parasite, it may
not be too late.  Well, I
am going to this festival. If possible, you also
come there to save the humans.
Now inside the festival,
that man in the form of Sivan's uncle suddenly
transforms himself into a monster. Everyone gets scared after seeing him.
And he starts killing the people present here.
Here it is shown that Yeon has also
found Kang Woo's sister. He tells Kang Woo's sister
that I do
not want to harm you, I just
came to help you.  Here is the man who was
involved with the Parasites only for money, he
starts coming to the Parasite with the Mayor so that the Parasite can
kill the Mayor and take his disguise and now before he can
kill the Parasite Mayor and take his face,
here  Kang Woo's sister arrives,
Kangoo's sister starts fighting on the other side
while Kang tries to save the mayor's life and
tries to take him away from here, in which Kangoo
succeeds but on the other side, Parasite's
Congo's monster-turned-sister is killed in the battle.
We see that the person in whose body
the parasite was present also dies,
and this parasite has no body, that is why the
military man who supported him is beheaded.  It takes over
her body and takes over her body. Here a
fight starts between Zion and that parasite. As we know earlier
that the parasite inside Zion is
not that powerful, so now she
was going to lose to the other parasite.  Before
the parasite can kill him, Joey comes from behind and
shoots him. Soon
many military officers come here.
Zion had become unconscious here, Cango
takes care of him and at this time Joey tries to get
Zion arrested.  Instead she tells everyone
that all the parasites here have been killed.
She saved Zion
because she knew that Zion does
n't harm anyone. All the parasites were destroyed and
everything became normal. Gang
Woo is also now on The Gray Team.  He
had joined Joe and he also invites Zion to join his team.
In the last part of the series, it is
shown that now a Japanese
man has come to meet Joe and
this story ends here.