So the story starts with showing a plane
in which a girl named Katia was
going to Russia with her mother.
During the journey, Katia got blinded but when she
opened her eyes, she came to know that there was
something wrong in the plane.  When she looked around,
she couldn't see her mom anywhere.
Now suddenly it was announced in the plane
that the plane was
going to make an emergency landing shortly, due to which Kath got very
nervous and tried to find her mom.
When she looks back, she sees an old woman on the back seat.
She was reciting some mantra,
where suddenly the eyes of the old woman turn
white, seeing which Katia gets so scared
that she faints. Meanwhile, the
engine of the plane starts working.  Suddenly a fire breaks out due to which the
plane gets destroyed and falls down and
in this accident all the people lose their lives
except Katia because she was saved,
hence only Katia was being shown everywhere in the news
after which the story  In this,
we are shown the time after 20 years
where Katia is married and now
she has a daughter but even today the news reporters keep
harassing her to interview her. Now Katia
was with her daughter when  Here a news
reporter comes and starts talking to Katia about the plane accident that happened 20 years ago, to
which Katia replies that now I have
forgotten that accident, after which
Katia and her daughter went to the airport
because she wanted to stay in her family.  She was taking her daughter to her grandfather.
Looking at the plane, it seemed that there were
not many passengers in it.
Here Katia's daughter told him, "Mama, I
want to sit on the back seat", to which
she refused by saying, "No."  Son,
that Seth is not ours. Before the plane takes off,
Katia and her daughter meet a
report reporter.
Hearing about the bad weather, Kath was looking very upset,
so the reporter consoles her. Do
n't worry, nothing will happen, everything will be fine.
Even the bad weather will be fine. Now Kadya
notices that there is noise in the row behind us.
In fact, there was an old lady who was not
feeling well. She was having panic attacks.
She was
very afraid of traveling by plane.  Now, because Katya
was a doctor of the mind, she goes to the old woman and
takes care of her. She also
gives her the same anti-stress medicine which
she herself used to take. Now
in the front row of the plane, we see a man who is a
big businessman.  She
saw a boy sitting on her seat in the seventh row, who was
an artist and was
painting. The plane
moved forward to take off. Kadiya was also in the washroom
when she heard her mother's voice.  A voice came,
as she opened the door, she came to a house
which was actually the same house where
Katia used to live with her mom. She
roams around in this entire house and as she
opens the door to go out of the house, she comes back to the
same house.  Katya was quite surprised to see what she saw in the plane. As she
moved forward, she saw that the
exit from the Amer Acensie was
blocked; soon the air
hostess came and asked her to sit on her seat,
where the reporter said this to Katya.  He
tries to ask why are you getting so worried
but she does
n't answer anything. Then here Katia's
daughter tells the reporter about her plane
accident and now after some
time the clouds turn red.  They start coming with the
strangest thing. A lot of hands come on their windows.
Katia was also sleeping
where she has a dream again. In her dream
we now see little Thea who was sitting and
eating food with her mother and this.  The time
was after the plane accident. Katia asked her mother whether the
mark on her leg would
disappear soon. Her
mother replied, "I don't know, son. It is
possible that it may never go away, it will always be
on your leg."  Just then Katia looks at the big mirror in front of her,
in which her mother's reflection looks
very ugly, hence, Kadya
asks her mom, 'Did
you die in the plane crash? Hearing this, her mom
felt very bad, so she asks Katia to see her.  She
comes closer and says that you should stop asking me such useless
questions because it has been
three months since the plane accident and now when
her mom was washing the utensils, Katia
starts hearing strange downy sounds.  She
looked at him, his head starts
shaking strangely, then
his mother turns her neck badly and starts shaking Katia.
With this terrible dream, Katia's
eyes opened, she was very scared at the present moment,
now suddenly there is a small jerk in the plane.
It seems, but due to this, all the passengers become
very nervous. Now the health of the old lady's
husband suddenly becomes so bad
that he becomes unconscious, so
along with the stewardess, all the passengers also go to help him,
where Katia helps the man.  She
makes Kath lie down on the ground to give him CPR due to
which suddenly the man regains consciousness but
his eyes were also white. Now he starts
shaking vigorously. Suddenly he gets up and holds Kath.
Ajit starts chanting mantras in his ears.
After doing this, he once
again fell down but here Katia was very
nervous because she had again
seen the white eyes which she had
seen of that old woman in her childhood. She was thinking about this and that is why she was
following that reporter.  A hand is
visible and she goes into deep thought
during which the old man dies. Due to
bad weather, the plane was also
going out of control, so the air
hostess asked everyone to sit on their respective seats.  She
asks to put on the oxygen mask.
Just as the passengers are about to approach, there is a
strong shock due to which the air hostess
hits the ceiling and falls down and
becomes unconscious there. Meanwhile,
due to lack of oxygen, Katia gradually
becomes unconscious.  Where in her mind she started
seeing the same old woman again. Now after some time,
Kath had regained consciousness and the plane was also under
control, so Kath quickly
got up and went to her daughter. The girl was crying a lot.
That's why Katia starts taking care of her,
then a reporter comes to Katia and asks
what happened to you suddenly, on
which Katia tells him about that old woman and
says that
when that plane accident happened to me in my childhood, then that was the same.
Some time ago in the plane, I had seen an old
woman with white eyes who was
reciting a mantra and the
husband of that old woman had whispered the same mantra in my ear.
Further, Kadia tells him that I
believe that the old woman is angry with me.
Because everyone except me was killed in that plane accident,
that is why now the soul of that old woman
wants to kill me. After hearing all this, the
reporter says that look, you should
not get worried by thinking anything like this and yes,
you do this and also take your medicine.  Stop it
because I think because of those pills
you are getting hallucinations i.e.
you are seeing thoughts which have no
connection with reality. After this
Katia went to her daughter who
was drawing a drawing of a plane.  Her
daughter had also prepared a seat for row number 19
on which she was insisting to go and sit, on
which she clearly refused. Now
Katia was feeling that
before the plane took off because  I heard my mom's
voice, so it means that she is trying to tell me about something or something.
Now the businessman
tells the artist that I have been traveling for the last one
week, now I just want to be with my
family.  Saying that he wants to go closer, he
shows the picture of his family on his mobile to the artist, but the artist
was so strange that he did not pay even the slightest attention to it, he was
busy in making his drawings, then we saw that the artist was
currently working with the businessman.
Katia is drawing. She sees that her daughter is
talking to someone on the back seat, but
now when Katia wakes up and looks, she does
not see anyone sitting on the back seat. Now
on asking, Katia's daughter tells that the
back seat is  But there is a girl sitting who is
telling me that your mom will
leave you. Hearing this, Katia
hugs her daughter and explains that my
love, my daughter, I will
not leave you and go anywhere. Then the hostess comes and announces
that there is a storm.  As if the plane was being
landed in Nova, this was actually the same place
where 20 years ago Katia was going with her mom.
Now here Katia was getting suspicious of the air hostess
because she had
heard about the death of the old woman's husband.  Had
not told the pilot. After some time we
saw that a cylinder was leaking under the businessman's set.
Now suddenly the businessman
takes out his cigarette and starts smoking.
Seeing him, Kadya understood the whole thing. She got scared and
immediately got up to stop him but  By then it was
too late because the businessman had lit the
lighter. As soon as this happens, the gas
catches fire due to which the businessman starts burning completely.
Katia sees a face like a drunkard in the fire
who was staring at her and shouting
at her. Now only then.  Here the air hostess comes and
quickly extinguishes the fire, which
saves the businessman's life, but he gets completely
burnt. Meanwhile, Kath sees a shadow
which was going towards his daughter.
Seeing this, he quickly  She
started going to her daughter but she found herself
sitting in front of her, with whom she went
into thoughts that the time was
a day before she boarded the plane, where Katia was
with her daughter. Here we saw that
Katia  Even today, there is a scar on her leg
which was formed due to injury in the plane crash, with which
she
came out of her thoughts, where Katia was continuously looking at a place,
when her daughter came to the garden and
asked.  Hey Mama, why are you doing this? Why are
you continuously looking at one place?
You were so engrossed in looking at that place that
you didn't even notice where I was.
Hearing this, Katia says sorry, my daughter
and hugs her.  Potter comes to Katia and
tells her that the businessman's condition has become
worse, so come quickly, he
needs your help. His eyes also
fall on the artist, who
was still engrossed in his work.  Katia was
drawing while speaking.
Seeing his behavior like this, Katya gets more upset,
so she started shouting at the artist,
but even this did not make any difference to her,
but seeing Katya so upset, the reporter
comes to her and takes care of her. Now the businessman
somehow helps her.
Seeing that the artist was trying to reach his phone, he
got up and started showing the phone to the businessman
in which there was a
picture of the businessman's family. Actually, the businessman
was about to die but in his last moments he
wanted to see his family.  As
soon as he finds peace, he smiles and
with that he loses his life. After some time,
Kadiya comes to the artist and
apologizes to him that I behaved like this with you,
sorry for that. Then Kadiya
notices that the old woman is
While she was not sitting on the seat, she remembered that yes, the
old lady had gone to the washroom a long time ago. She was being
troubled by the fact that she had
not yet returned from the washroom, so in tension,
Katia started banging the washroom door loudly.
Seeing this, the air hostess feels
as if Katia's mind and weight are
not right, so she asks her to go back to the seat and
sit but she does not agree and still
insists on opening the door, so the air
hostess quickly opens the door.
But Kath does not find the old woman inside.
Now when Katia was standing near the old woman's husband,
she sees that suddenly the
man's eyes open which are still white
and he suddenly attacks Thea.
As soon as Katya
moved back a little, she fell on her back, then
a lot of black hands came and
started trying to catch Katya, due to which she got very scared and
started screaming, but in the meantime she had
noticed that I was row number 19.  But
I am actually in my childhood, when the plane accident
happened, at that time too, Katia's seat was on row 19
and now after some time,
when Katia regains consciousness, she gets up from that seat and
sees that the old woman's husband.  The dead body is
still lying in front of her, it is the same as it was
and now when she moves ahead, she again
sees someone's shadow due to which she gets
very scared. She quickly comes to her daughter and
says that we have just got to the plane.
Seeing that he would have to leave, the reporter tried to stop him,
but suddenly his eyes started
bleeding, with which he
became unconscious, then suddenly an air hostess
also started watering from her mouth, she
started yearning for this air hostess.  Her eyes
had also turned white and she fell on the ground and
died. Katia felt strange here,
so she quickly ran
to the artist and snatched the book of his drawings and started
looking at it. Yes, she realized that the
artist had-  All the people who had made the drawings have
died, hence it was
Kati's turn to do the next thing, now before
Katia could get some worship from the artist, her
body gets burnt and suddenly turns into ashes.
She got so scared that she quickly took care of her daughter.  She grabs his
hand and
starts going to the pilot's cabin. Although the air
hostess and the reporter were forbidding her to do so,
she does not stop. Now suddenly an
unknown force takes the air hostess away and
takes her with it.
Bleeding also starts coming from the pilot's head, which becomes so
much that he collapses there and
dies on the spot.
Obviously, seeing this, Katia becomes more nervous and
now she breaks the door of the pilot's cabin,
but to do so  Even after this, she
finds not the pilot's cabin but another cabin of the plane where it was empty all day
and it was exactly the same cabin as the
plane of her childhood. Now again Katia
moves ahead and opens the pilot's cabin
but she  Again, she
gets a plane cabin with seats. By doing this again and again, she
was coming to the passenger cabin only, due to
which Katia felt as if she was
stuck in a loop, this thing is not ending, it is
happening again and again.  But now
suddenly Katia sees that my daughter is
sitting on row number 19, who was calling her mom
to her. Now then Katia
sees a Sai very close to her daughter, so to
save her daughter, she quickly runs.  She
runs towards that place where she saw that it was
none other than the shadow of the same old woman,
that is, whom she had seen in her childhood before the plane was destroyed.
Here the elder woman
tells Katya that at that time when the plane was about to be
destroyed, I  I had put you to sleep
because at that time I did not want
you or your mother to die,
but your mother had died in that plane crash,
so now I want
you to go to the past and learn about the things that happened at that time of the plane crash.  She
says this and the old woman frees Katia from her magic,
that is, now Katia's
fate was in her own hands. Well, now
we saw that Katia comes back to her past at the
time when the plane crash
occurs.  Here all the same passengers were
sitting who were traveling with Katia even in the present time. The
old woman and
her husband were sitting on the back seat of Katia,
then the old woman's husband
had a heart attack, hence Katia.  Mom
goes to help her, that is, just as
Katia had helped people in the present time,
similarly in the past,
Katia's mom was also helping them all.
In the present time, Katia's daughter helps her to
sit on row number 19.  Kath was being told so that Kath
and her mom could save their lives in the past
where only Kath survived but her mom was
killed after which Katia once again
goes back to herself when she
was a child where we see the destruction of the plane.  The
same scene which we had
seen in the beginning is shown, here Katia's mother
becomes unconscious, then somehow Katia
pulls her mom and makes her lie down on row number 19,
after which the plane gets destroyed and
all the people in it are killed.  People were killed except two and
that was Kadiya and her mom and with this the
story of this film ends here.