As the story begins, we meet a girl named Diana.
Look at the woman whose daughter"s condition is very bad.
bad because he was born prematurely
She was in the incubator at this time. She was breathing.
It was coming with great difficulty, that"s why
How long will she be alive in this situation? Scene cut
And after 17 years we see the same child. This child"s name is Loi. She is shown. This child"s name is Loi. She is grown up and was born prematurely. She is grown up and was born prematurely. She is grown up and was born prematurely. Many parts of her body are not working. She is also suffering from asthma and heart disease. Chloe has to take a lot of medicines to keep her life normal. She is also suffering from asthma and heart disease. Chloe has to take a lot of medicines to keep her life normal. Medicines
Chloe needs a lot of medicines to keep her busy
Lots of medicines to keep Chloe on
Have to accept all these complications
Despite this, Chloe is quite intelligent, she is a big
Wanted to take admission in university but
University of the application sent by him
She didn"t answer so he felt that
Mom just got home from grocery shopping.
She was busy in phone calls as soon as she came back.
Gets it and Chloe as soon as the grocery bag
If the bag is opened to take chocolates from
He found something in Tina"s name inside it.
Tablets are available after seeing which they
Didn"t use any tablet then after all
What would have happened to them in the night now?
Chloe comes to give him tablets
notices that she was given the same tablet
The one that came in her mom"s name was from Tina.
Asks if these tablets are in your name
She quietly takes the medicine the next morning.
Chloe from the same medicine medicine ruck
Takes out this medicine to check
His formula was written trioxyn but
The strange thing was that this medicine was sold to someone else.
Was rapped by medicine rapper and it
Now to find out that whole mystery
quickly search tri auxin on computer
It means it is written on the wrapper of that medicine.
She searches for formula but today her
Internet is not working on mom"s computer.
Tha we see that the internet is actually Tina
She comes to the room the next morning when she
sees that her mom is busy in the garden so she
quickly goes to her room and dials her mobile ...
It is very important that the person on the other side of the phone
does chloe"s work he tells her
That tablet of formula named Tri Oxon
This is often given to heart patients
There is a red color tablet but at this time
The tablet that was in Loi"s hand was green in color.
Anyhow the real formula of this medicine
Had to find out so that they could know about its side effects
That"s why he went to dinner thinking something.
K time tells Tana that there is plenty of time
Have we gone anywhere? Have we gone? Movie
Tia can go to the theater to see it
Then Chloe asked Tia to go to the washroom.
She leaves but doesn"t actually go to the washroom.
Rather went to a nearby pharmaceutical company
She goes to a medicine pharmacist
telling me about it
We have to find out what this is about
She refuses because this medicine is for her
Was it taken in mom"s name or from Chloe Farms?
She says I"m actually playing the Bang Mom game
He has given me this task that I
Please find the formula for this medicine and bring it.
Please if you help me I will
Hearing this, Forma tells him
Looking at the medicine, it is said that this medicine
It is used for dogs and if any
If a person takes these medicines he will become paralyzed
Maybe after hearing this Chloe will be very
She was very scared because there was no one in her house.
Due to distress and fear he even got an asthma attack.
She was breathing with difficulty and
At the same time, Tiha Na i.e. his mother also told him
She had come here searching and found a
renders unconscious while injecting and
Then she brings her home when she regains consciousness.
While outside Diana searches on her computer
Was trying to paralyze any person
How can it be done here, Chloe also has her own
I wanted to get out of the room when
An idea comes to mind that he
Go to the other room through the window
Fills cold water inside and from your window
jumps out with difficulty
While coloring she reached her mom"s room
So first of all he ironed his window.
After heating the rod and cooling it
Throwing water like windows break
She would have quickly gone out of this room.
And she opens the door of her room.
it became difficult to breathe again
She used her lure kept in this room.
And quickly come down the stairs
She tries hard but now it seems that
wears the wheel chair down first and then
She herself falls down the stairs.
There was a lot of injury at the time but it healed on its own.
Taking care of and sitting in the wheelchair again
goes out of the house to go out of the house
So she succeeded but with what help?
No, she goes out on the road and then
Chloe thought she heard a car.
That this is Tina"s car, that is why she is in the jungles.
I hid but it was actually a truck
She goes and stands in front of this truck
seeing which the truck driver would stop his truck
By giving him medicine for dogs since childhood
She is paralyzed and her life is in danger.
And she tells this man that I don"t want any
This man has to go to the police station in his condition
agrees before he
Riding Chloe in my truck from behind
Where are you taking my daughter?
In response to which this man says that
Your daughter thinks you wrong her
She is giving medicine against you.
Wants to go to police station and in this work
I will help her so Diana regains consciousness now.
But when this man doesn"t stop then he is forced to
Tana has to use the wrong way
And here"s Chloe"s about to faint.
Chloe gets home by injecting this man
Takes it back i.e. one more time Chloe
has reached that dangerous life
He was kept tied with chains and here he
She was also making a medicine so that she could cure Chloe.
Chloe could paralyze her forever.
That"s why I wanted to get out of here recently
Those are some important things inside the basement.
starts searching with the help of which she can reach here
In which his offer from the university
There was also a letter which his mother hid here
Chloe is very sad to see this.
Because this is the biggest thing of his life
It was a dream which his wax broke a little
And after searching, Chloe was found here in the hospital.
He comes to know by looking at the document.
That pre-mature girl named Chloe who from today
She was born 17 years ago, as soon as she was born
After a few hours she was killed here.
There was also a death certificate if the girl was killed.
Who was Chloe when she was gone?
Those people were crying because the day
Chloe was born inside the hospital on the same day
Their daughter was also born in the same hospital.
It happened and someone from the hospital
Kidnapped after seeing this news
Loi Jaan wants Tana to be her real mom.
Now she wants to get out of here but how?
All exit routes are closed during this time
But Tia also comes and Chloe sees her.
She gets scared and tells him to stay away from me.
I am gone, you are not my mom.
you kidnapped me from the hospital
you believe me you are my daughter
i love you so much i love you today
I won"t give you any such medicine again.
I want you to always be with me
But Chloe"s here again with Tana
If you misbehave then Tahna also gets angry.
Made his own to paralyze Chloe
medicine filled
To save myself, I crawled away from there.
A walk goes into the drawer, walk her
The drawer is unable to lock and locks itself.
Drink a liquid here to save yourself
Her condition had worsened and she was crying a lot.
Because she really considered Chloe her daughter.
Believed and sending Chloe away from me
Didn"t want to and she paralyzed Chloe
Medicine was also given to the to-be because of this
That he may not go to his real parents
Found you in the hospital, around him
Doctors were there and his stomach was being cleaned.
When he looked out of the room, he was there.
Tana was standing there, that is, she was the one who took him to the hospital.
She would have got scared again after seeing him.
And she calls the nurse standing nearby.
And this thing can also see Tiana outside.
Tiana knew that Chloe nursed her
I will tell you about it as soon as there is time.
sets off the hospital"s emergency alarm
goes into chaos in the hospital and
Taking advantage of this, he
When she came in she saw that Chloe was there.
No because Chloe gave her pen and paper too
Had asked for a nurse to tell me something
The direct suspicion was now on his mother.
hospital security quickly
Tia informs him here also
Tiana also gave her gun to the security
Take it out and point it at security
Let"s say I just want my daughter
I want to take you home, go away from me
By the way, when the gun had not gone down.
Forced the security to use their guns on him.
Chloe gets injured, doctors come here
Are rescued and are told that
Chloe, a year has passed since the whole incident.
Now in jail to visit her mom Tina
Which paralyzed Chloe for many years
Was arrested for keeping we see
She walks to Tia"s house and
She tells him that she will leave in some time.
I will get it after I finish the medicine given by you.
It turns out that Chloe some time later
Tina used to come to meet Tina at this time
tells that I have completed my studies
It"s over and I told my sleeping parents
Diana has also found it just silently
I kept listening to him, after this we
Let"s see that from inside Chloe"s mouth
Have taken out some wrapped tablets
Tablets that Diana used throughout her life
It was clear that he would take revenge from Tia.
And she doesn"t want that ever Diana
Came out of this jail and now showing this